[
  {
    "name": "Circle",
    "id": "circle",
    "scores": 0,
    "totalPS": 2,
    "psArray": [
      {
        "ps_no": 1,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": " Find area of green colored region",
            "options": [4, 5, 6, 7],
            "answer": 2,
            "cvData": [
              "mcq",
              "haha",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "Square Area = 10 \u00D7 10 = 100",
              "",

              "2×Half Circle = 1 Full Circle",
              "Circle Area = πr² = 78.53 ",
               "∴ Red Shaded Area ",
                "= 100 - 78.53 = 21.46",
              "",
              " Total Red area = ",
              "21.46×2 = 42.92cm " ,
              "∴ Green Area = 57.07 Ans."
            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "picker",
            "question": "One (Picker) of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [100, 10, 150],
            "answer": 120,
            "cvData": [
              "picker",
              "hehe",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "solu \n tion",
              "new line happens \n sol2",
              "solution",
              "solution",
              "solufsfsfsdfsdfstion",
              "solsdfsfsghfhfdfution",
              "sortjlonl2"
            ],
            "score": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "ps_no": 2,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "Which country won every Olympic Men’s hockey gold medal from 1928 to 1956?",
            "options": [
              "App",
              "android",
              "Visual",
              "fiber"
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "try again",
              "not found"
            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [
              "Application",
              "android1",
              "Visual",
              "physics"
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "see later",
              "found"
            ],
            "score": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Rectangle",
    "id": "rectangle",
    "scores": 0,
    "totalPS": 3,
    "psArray": [
      {
        "ps_no": 1,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": " area of rectangle ??",
            "options": [
              "23",
              "Blue Cheese2",
              "Gorgonzola",
              "wrong question"
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "sol",
              "later solute"
            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [
              "fsfsf",
              "dfgdgg Cheese",
              "dsfsfsdd",
              "Parmesan"
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "solution",
              "sol2"
            ],
            "score": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "ps_no": 2,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "Which country won every Olympic Men’s hockey gold medal from 1928 to 1956?",
            "options": [
              "App",
              "android",
              "Visual",
              "fiber"
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "try again",
              "not found"
            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [
              "Application",
              "android1",
              "Visual",
              "physics"
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "see later",
              "found"
            ],
            "score": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "ps_no": 3,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "Which country won every Olympic Men’s hockey gold medal from 1928 to 1956?",
            "options": [
              "App",
              "android",
              "Visual",
              "fiber"
            ],
            "answer": 3,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "try again",
              "not found"
            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [
              "Application",
              "android1",
              "Visual",
              "physics"
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "see later",
              "found"
            ],
            "score": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Percentage",
    "id": "percent",
    "scores": 0,
    "totalPS": 2,
    "psArray": [
      {
        "ps_no": 1,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "The population of a village increases from 675 to 783. Find the percentage increase.",
            "options": [14, 15, 16, 17],
            "answer": 3,
            "cvData": [
              "Population Increase = 783 - 675 = 108",
              "Percentage Increase = x%",
              "x = 16"
            ],
            "solution": [

            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "picker",
            "question": "One (Picker) of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [100, 10, 150],
            "answer": 120,
            "cvData": [
              "picker",
              "hehe",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "solu \n tion",
              "new line happens \n sol2",
              "solution",
              "solution",
              "solufsfsfsdfsdfstion",
              "solsdfsfsghfhfdfution",
              "sortjlonl2"
            ],
            "score": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "ps_no": 2,
        "qnArray": [
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "Which country won every Olympic Men’s hockey gold medal from 1928 to 1956?",
            "options": [
              "App",
              "android",
              "Visual",
              "fiber"
            ],
            "answer": 4,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "try again",
              "not found"
            ],
            "score": 0
          },
          {
            "type": "mcq",
            "question": "One of the fattiest fishes is salmon. 4 ounces contains how many grams of fat?",
            "options": [
              "Application",
              "android1",
              "Visual",
              "physics"
            ],
            "answer": 1,
            "cvData": [
              "Canada",
              "Russia",
              "India",
              "USA"
            ],
            "solution": [
              "see later",
              "found"
            ],
            "score": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }

]
